lax.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy & Cookie Policy

As of March 24, 2018 we have updated our privacy and cookie policy to adhere to General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

Lax.com Privacy & Cookie Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from https://www.lax.com (the “Site”).

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

At LAX.com, your privacy is our top priority. Our only goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our services. When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

\- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

\- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.

\- “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, Paypal and Apple Pay), email address, and phone number.  We refer to this information as “Order Information.”

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). 

Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

Communicate with you;

Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and

When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

CREDIT CARD SECURITY

We guarantee that you will be able to use your credit card securely while shopping at LAX.com. All important and private financial and personal information is encrypted before it is transmitted to us from our secure cart page. Encrypted personal information can not be read or recorded as it is being transmitted over the internet.

YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We DO NOT Sell or Rent your Information.  We only share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use and organize your Personal Information, as described above.  For example, we use Magento to power our online store--you can read more about how Magento uses your Personal Information here: https://magento.com/legal/terms/privacy

We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:  https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. 

You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here:  [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

We use Hubspot for our Customer Relationship Management (CRM).  This allows us to hold your customer data in a secure database. It helps us understand how our customers use the site and it is the email platform we use to send marketing information.

You can read more about Hubspot’s Privacy Policy here: [https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy](https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy?__hstc=237103263.5d7844f464e5e5c288abbdab4d759f25.1546545962326.1551900732178.1551902775451.31&__hssc=237103263.17.1551902775451&__hsfp=3601253023)

You can Opt-out of Hubspot and email marketing here: http://info.lax.com/hs/manage-preferences/unsubscribe-simple?via_redirect=true

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by:

    FACEBOOK - <https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads>

    GOOGLE - <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous>

    BING - <https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads>

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:  <http://optout.aboutads.info/>.

DO NOT TRACK

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

YOUR RIGHTS

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including the United States.

DATA RETENTION

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

MINORS

The Site is intended for individuals of all ages and we keep the content age appropriate.  We suggest children consult parents before sharing any information or ordering on our site. 

TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS

In the event that a Lax.com product is mistakenly listed at an incorrect price, Lax.com reserves the right to refuse or cancel any orders placed for product listed at the incorrect price. Lax.com reserves the right to refuse or cancel any such orders.

CHANGES

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

EXTERNAL LINKS

The Site may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that the Site is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites. Websites that are accessible by hyperlinks from the Site that may use cookies. The Site encourages you to read the privacy statements provided by other websites before you provide personally identifiable information to them.

CONTACT US

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at questions@lax.com or by mail using the details provided below:

Lax.com LLC

345 Wilson Ave, 

Norwalk, CT, 06460

United States

855-255-5294
